replug.io 2019-07-01

# Replug.io | Privacy

Last updated: **24 May, 2018**

## 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use, and share your information across our websites, APIs, email notifications, applications and our other covered services that link to this Policy (collectively, the “Services”) and from our white label partners and other third parties. 

For example, you send us information when you use our Services on the web, via our API, or from our mobile apps. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure, and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This includes any information you choose to provide that is deemed sensitive under applicable law. 

Your information is controlled by Replug, a product of Replug Inc, Regeringsgatan 65, 111 56, Stockholm, Sweden. However, you alone control and are responsible for any content you submit, create or post through the Services, as provided in the [Terms of Service](https://replug.io/terms.php). Replug is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy regarding all information that might be collected while using any of our Services. 

When this policy mentions “we” or “us,” it refers to the processor of your information under this policy. We collect personal information with consent, when appropriate or required, and by lawful means only. 

Irrespective of which country you live in, you authorize us to transfer, store, and use your information in any country where we operate.  If there is a case when personal data is transferred from the EU to the United States, it is solely for the purpose of processing as per instructions from the controller. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please submit a request through our form, available at <https://replug.io/contact>. 

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.  

## 2\. Information that you give to Replug

We require certain information to provide our Services to you. For example, you must have an account in order to create or post shortened links through Replug. When you choose to share the information below with us, we collect and use it to operate our Services. 

### 2.1 Basic Account Information

You might give Replug information about yourself by filling in forms on our Services or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. 

This includes information provided when you:

  * Register to use our website
  * Subscribe to our Services
  * Download educational content
  * Search for a product or service
  * Participate in discussion forums
  * Register for a webinar
  * Enter a competition, promotion or survey
  * Sign up to our training program
  * Submit a ticket to our support team

If you do choose to create an account, you must provide us with some personal data so that we can provide our Services to you. The personal information you give us is limited to your name, address, email address, a password, phone number, credit card details and photograph. None of the personal information you provide is shared publicly.  

### 2.2 Contact Information and Mailing Lists

We use your personal contact information, such as your email address to authenticate your account and keep it - and our Services - secure, and to help prevent spam, fraud, and abuse.  We also use contact information to personalize our Services, enable certain account features and to send you information about our Services. If you provide us with your phone number, you agree to receive calls to that number to discuss matters that impact your usage of our Services. You can update your notification settings to control notifications you receive from Replug. You can also unsubscribe from an email notification by following the instructions contained within the email. 

If you email us, we will keep the content of your message, your email address, and your contact information to respond to your request. 

### 2.3 Payment Information

You may provide us with payment information, including your credit or debit card number, PayPal address, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address, in order to pay for your subscription or for the purchase of other offerings provided as part of our services. 

This information is passed securely to our payment processor, Fastspring Inc., and after a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, ﬁnancials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

We may, however, store your invoices and receipts for a period of up to 5 years to facilitate our legal obligation to provide accounting information to the tax authorities for tax purposes. 

## 3\. Information we collect about you

### 3.1 Location Information

With regard to each of your visits to our Services, we may automatically collect information about your login and current location, which we get from signals such as your IP address or device settings, to securely and reliably set up and maintain your account and to provide our services to you. We also store your time zone settings in order to ensure our Services operate correctly. 

### 3.2 Links and Product Usage

In order to operate our services, we keep track of how you interact with links across our Services. This includes links in emails we send you as well as actions you take when using different features within the products we offer. 

### 3.3 Photos

When you connect your social media profile to Replug, we may collect and store the link to your avatar. We use this data in order to deliver our Services to you. 

### 3.4 Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other visitors and users on our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. We use information held about you in the following ways: 

#### 3.4.1  Information you give to us

We will use this information:

  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us; 
  * to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about; 
  * to notify you about changes to our Services; 
  * to ensure that content from our Services is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device. 

#### 3.4.2  Information we collect about you

We will use this information:

  * to administer our Services and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes; 
  * to improve our Services to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Services, when you choose to do so; 
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Services safe and secure; 
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; 
  * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Services about product features that may interest you or them. 

#### 3.4.3 Information we receive from other sources

We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above, depending on the types of information we receive. For example, when tracking referrals from our affiliate partners, the cookies stored on your browser allow us to reward affiliates for introducing you to our Service. 

### 3.5 Log Data

We receive information when you view content on our website or interact with our Services, even if you have not created an account. For example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, interact with our email notifications, we may collect information about you. 

This log data stored includes information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, device information (including device and application IDs), and cookie information. 

We use this data to operate our Services and ensure their secure, reliable, and robust performance. For example, we use log data to protect the security of accounts, improve the quality of our products and to determine which features are being used most on our Services. 

We may also record your usage of our Services using screencasting tools in order to improve our Services and deliver a better user experience.  With regard to each of your visits to our Services we may automatically collect the following log data: 

Technical information

  * (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet
  * Login information
  * Browser type and version
  * Time zone setting
  * Browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform.

Information about your visit:

  * Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time) 
  * Products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages 
  * Page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs) and methods used to browse away from the page 
  * Any phone number used to call our customer service number
  * A video recording of your web session whilst browsing our website

## 4\. How we use your information

We are passionate about building useful tools to help businesses and agencies be more efficient and productive when managing social media at scale. We use all of the information we have to help us provide and support our Services. Here’s how: 

### 4.1. Provide, improve and develop Services

We are able to deliver our Services, support your usage of our products and introduce improvements by using this information to understand how you use and interact with our Services. 

When we have location information, we use it to tailor our Services for you and others, like automatically detecting your location in order to support your ability to schedule messages in your own time zone. 

We conduct surveys and research, test features in development, and analyze the information we have to evaluate and improve products and services, develop new products or features, and conduct audits and troubleshooting activities. 

### 4.2. Communicate with you

We use your information to send you marketing communications, communicate with you about our Services and let you know about our policies and terms. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us. 

## 5\. Information we receive from other sources

We may receive information about you if you use any of the Services we provide. We inform you when we collect any data that it may be shared internally and combined with other data collected on our Services. For example, when you connect your Facebook account to Replug, you will be able to opt in to the data that Replug is able to collect from Facebook on your behalf. 

We may also receive private information about your business profiles from the social network profiles you connect to Replug including Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google+, Tumblr, and Instagram. 

We may also access data from your Google Analytics account in real time when you authorize this from our reporting area. 

On all occasions where we receive data from a platform with whom our Services integrate, you will be informed of the data that will be collected by our Services and will need to give consent to have Replug receive and process your personal data from these platforms on your behalf.  

We work closely with other third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them. The information we receive is used to enhance your experience with our Services. 

## 6\. Information we share and disclose

We do not sell or trade your personally identiﬁable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Services, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information conﬁdential and are compliant with GDPR. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

Non-personally identiﬁable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### 6.1 Sharing you control

We share or disclose your personal data with your consent or at your direction, such as when you authorize a social network or third party application to access your account or when you direct us to share your feedback with a business. 

When you share content via your Replug account to a third-party service, keep in mind that you are controlling the flow of this content from our platform through to the third-party service. 

When you add a team member or client to your account, you may choose to share personal data with them. For example, you may choose to share a client’s analytics report with a team member. By acting as data controller, Replug provides you with all the tools and settings you need to be able to control the flow of data. 

Subject to your settings, we also provide certain third parties with personal data to help us offer or operate our Services. 

### 6.2 Service providers and advertisers

We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us in the United States, UK, and other countries. For example, we use a variety of third-party services to help operate our services, such as hosting our various blogs and websites, and to help us understand the use of our services, such as Google Analytics. 

We may share your private personal data with such service providers subject to obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions. 

We share your payment information with payment services providers to process payments; prevent, detect, and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities; facilitate dispute resolution such as chargebacks or refunds; and for other purposes associated with the acceptance of credit and debit cards. 

We may share your information with advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.  We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to display relevant advertisements to you on third party websites. For example, if we’ve noticed that you’ve been actively using our reporting features, we may use this data to show you relevant advertisements on Facebook informing you of a new analytics feature we’ve launched. 

### 6.3 Affiliates and change of ownership

In the event that we are involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets, your personal data may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. This Privacy Policy will apply to your personal data as transferred to the new entity. 

We may also disclose personal data about you to our affiliates in order to help operate our services and our affiliates’ services. This information is limited to your email address, browsing behavior and any other actions you’ve taken on our website before becoming a customer. 

## 7\. Where we store and transfer your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by employees or contractors operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, processing your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. 

We take the protection of your data very seriously and have made every effort to be compliant with [ General Data Protection Regulation](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation) (GDPR) which is a “regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union and the EEA region.” The GDPR replaces the [1995 Data Protection Directive](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Data_Protection_Directive)  . We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers located in the US and certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using TLS technology and processed via our payment gateway, FastSpring. We do not store any credit cards in our system. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password(s) with anyone. We also provide additional security controls within Replug, allowing you to restrict access to specific IP addresses. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information on the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Services, and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

If you would like to request a list of sub-processors we use, you can do so via the following form:   <https://replug.io/contact>. 

## 8\. Your rights

Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have the right to access, rectify, port and erase your personal data. 

### 8.1 Accessing or Rectifying Your Personal Data

If you have registered an account on Replug, we provide you with tools and account settings to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal data you provided to us and associated with your account.  

### 8.2 Deletion

We store data until it is no longer necessary to provide our Services or until your account is deleted - whichever comes first. 

When deactivated, you will no longer be able to access your account across any of our Services. For up to 90 days after deactivation, it is still possible to restore your Replug account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated. The same applies to team members or client accounts you delete from within Replug. 

If you require immediate deletion of your account, please  [contact us using this](https://replug.io/contact) form and allow up to 72 hours for us to action your request.  When your account is deleted, we also delete all content you’ve created within your account, including all content created by team members and clients, and you won't be able to recover that information later. We will also delete any personally identifiable information stored in any third party applications we use to service your account. 

If you don't want to delete your account but want to temporarily stop using our Services, you can contact us to deactivate your account for a maximum of 90 days. 

### 8.3 Object, Restrict, or Withdraw Consent

When using any of our Services that require login information, if you would like to withdraw consent, please [contact us](https://replug.io/contact) and we will deactivate your account for you. 

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You may also opt out of Replug marketing communications sent to you by opening any email we have sent you and clicking on the Unsubscribe link. 

### 8.4 Portability

Replug provides you with a facility to download the content you have created or data retrieved from your analytics through any of our Services. If you would like further assistance exporting your data, please contact us at support@replug.io. 

### 8.5 Additional Information or Assistance

Our Services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to other websites. 

## 9\. Contact us

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to our Data Protection Officer, Waqar Azeem, at privacy@replug.io.  

You can also reach out by mail at: Replug Inc, c/o Sup46, 3rd Floor, Regeringsgatan 65, 111 56, Stockholm, Sweden 

## 10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our processing of your personal data and will always be at <https://replug.io/privacy>. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via email to the email address associated with your account. 

If you have not accepted our latest Privacy Policy, the account owner will be prompted to consent to the updated version when signing into their Replug account for the first time after a policy change. 

By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
